Jake Pasternak

jdp.pasternak@gmail.com • 808-216-3534 • linkedin.com/in/jakepasternak • github.com/jdpasternak

SUMMARY

Confident and charismatic leader with drive and will to grow in a role where his talents, skills, and visions fuel consistent achievement that benefits the company and its people. Experience in desktop/server administration, networking, and web development.

SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS

- **Platforms:** <u>A+</u>, Windows 7, 8/8.1, 10, Mac OS X, and Linux
- Productivity Suites: MS Office/365, Access, SharePoint, MS 365 Admin
- Server: Windows Server 2016, Ubuntu Server, Dell PowerEdge
- Networking: <u>Network+</u>, CCENT, Cisco IOS, VLANs, Subnetting, VPNs, DNS
- Security: <u>Security+</u>, <u>Pentest+</u>, Malware Analysis

- Programming/Scripting: Python, PowerShell, Java, JS, React, Express.js, Node.js PHP, .NET, SQL, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, JQuery, Bootstrap
- Web: Django, WordPress, hosting, design, admin
- Virtualization: VMWare Workstation 14, VirtualBox, Hyper-V
- ITSM/LCM: ServiceNow, TFS
- Automation/Logging: Elastic Stack, Ansible
- Cloud: <u>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner</u>, Azure, AWS

EXPERIENCE

IT Project Administrator (Full-Time) – Hawaii Medical Service Association (HMSA), Honolulu, HI DEC 2019 – Present

• <u>Project Management:</u> Planned, scheduled, and managed deployment of laptops to over 800 staff, including converting from virtual desktop to VPN. Spearheaded IT departments transition from in-office to working from home.

IT Project Coordinator (Contract) – Hawaii Medical Service Association (HMSA), Honolulu, HI APR 2019 – DEC 2019

 <u>Project Management:</u> Planned, scheduled, and managed org-wide conversion of desktop systems from Windows 7 to Windows 10; coordinated scheduling, communication, and reporting; leveraged PowerShell scripting to automate tasks; developed training and usage guides for new Windows 10 system for over 1200 staff.

Advanced Repair Agent – Geek Squad, Honolulu, HI

APR 2017 - SEP 2020

 Custom PC builds and upgrades; Hardware and software installations; Apple iOS and iPhone repair; Customer engagement.

IT Instructor – Advanced Computer Technology Training (ACTT Hawaii), Honolulu, HI

JUN 2018 - JAN 2019

• Developed and presented training plans and materials for instructing on CompTIA A+ certifications objectives.

Owner - JDP Enterprises, LLC, Honolulu, HI

SEP 2017 – Present

• Desktop repair services; Small office/Home office networking; Mail migrations; MS 365 Administration; Remote support; web design and development; online card capture and payment systems integration.

EDUCATION

AS in Computer, Security, and Networking Technologies

MAY 2020

Honolulu Community College

Honolulu, HI

Hardware and Software Troubleshooting • Information Security • Advanced Cisco Networking • Programming and Scripting • System Administration • Telecommunication • Ethical Hacking • Malware Analysis and Reverse Engineering